Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Programs for Basketball Games, V
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1980 (Box-folder 26-13)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1981 (Box-folder 27-1)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1982 (Box-folder 27-2)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1984 (Box-folder 27-3)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1985 (Box-folder 27-4)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1986 (Box-folder 27-5)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1987 (Box-folder 27-6)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1989 (Box-folder 27-7)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1990 (Box-folder 27-8)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1993 (Box-folder 27-9)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1995 (Box-folder 27-10)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1996 (Box-folder 27-11)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1997 (Box-folder 27-12)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.C.A.A., 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27-13)
- Scorebooks of Team Sports Events, VI
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 28-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1952 (Box-folder 28-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1953 (Box-folder 28-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 28-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 28-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 28-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1959 (Box-folder 28-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 28-8)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 28-9)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 28-10)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 28-11)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28-12)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 29-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 29-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 29-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 29-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 29-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 29-8)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 29-9)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 29-10)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 30-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 30-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 30-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 30-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 30-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 30-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 30-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 30-8)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 30-9)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 30-10)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 31-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 31-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 31-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 31-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 31-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 31-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 31-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 31-8)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 31-9)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 31-10)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 32-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 32-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 32-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 32-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 32-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 32-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 32-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 33-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 33-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 33-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 33-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 33-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 33-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 33-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 33-8)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 33-9)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 33-10)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 33-11)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 33-12)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Women, 1992 (Box-folder 33-13)
  - Scorebooks—Football, 1971-1998 (Box-folder 33-14)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 34-1)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 34-2)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 34-3)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 34-4)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 34-5)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 34-6)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 34-7)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 34-8)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 34-9)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 34-10)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 34-11)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 34-12)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 34-13)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 34-14)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 34-15)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1969 (Box-folder 35-1)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1969 (Box-folder 35-2)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 35-3)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 35-4)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1971 (Box-folder 35-5)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 35-6)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 35-7)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 35-8)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 35-9)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 35-10)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 35-11)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 35-12)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1987 (Box-folder 35-13)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling, 1988 (Box-folder 35-14)
  - Scorebooks – Wrestling (Box-folder 35-15)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-2)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-3)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-4)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-5)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-6)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-7)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-8)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-9)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 36 (oversized)-10)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-1)
  - Scorebooks – Basketball, Men, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-2)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-3)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-4)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-5)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-6)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-7)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-8)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-9)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-10)
  - Scorebooks – Swimming, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-11)
  - Scorebooks – Baseball, 1979 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-12)
  - Scorebooks – Baseball, 1979 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-13)
  - Scorebooks – Baseball, 1980 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-14)
  - Scorebooks – Track and Field, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 37 (oversized)-15)
- Miscellaneous Records, VII
  - Athletic Camp Contracts, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 38-1)
  - Baseball - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box-folder 38-2)
  - Baseball - Score Cards, 2001 (Box-folder 38-3)
  - Baseball - Play-by-play Records, 2001 (Box-folder 38-4)
  - Baseball – Schedule, rosters and stats, 2001 (Box-folder 38-5)
  - Camps – Brochures, 1990 (Box-folder 38-6)
  - Camps – Brochures, 1991 (Box-folder 38-7)
  - Men’s basketball, Certificates, 1957 (Box-folder 38-8)
  - Men’s basketball, Miscellaneous, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 38-9)
  - Men’s basketball, Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 38-10)
  - Men’s basketball, Miscellaneous Telegrams and Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 38-11)
  - Men’s basketball, Miscellaneous Telegrams and Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 38-12)
  - Men’s basketball, Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 38-13)
  - Football – Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 39-1)
  - Football—Miscellaneous, All-American Certificate, 1948 (Box-folder 39-2)
  - Football—Miscellaneous (Box-folder 39-3)
  - Miscellaneous photocopies (Box-folder 39-4)
  - Miscellaneous trading cards (Box-folder 39-5)
  - Paramedic Training – Agreements, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 39-6)
  - Paramedic Training – Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 39-7)
  - Paramedic Training – Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 39-8)
  - Softball – Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box-folder 39-9)
  - Student Athletic Training Camp, 1999 (Box-folder 39-10)
  - Student Athletic Training Camp, 2000 (Box-folder 40-1)
  - Team of the Week Certificates, 1995 (Box-folder 40-2)
  - Volleyball – Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 40-3)
  - Washington State Traffic Safety Commission – Procedures Manual, 1980 (Box-folder 40-4)
  - Women’s Basketball – Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 40-5)
  - Women’s Soccer – Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 40-6)
  - Wrestling – Miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 40-7)
- Photographs and Negatives of Athletics Teams, VIII
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1980 (Box-folder 41-1)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1981 (Box-folder 41-2)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1982 (Box-folder 41-3)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1983 (Box-folder 41-4)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1984 (Box-folder 41-5)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1985 (Box-folder 41-6)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1986 (Box-folder 41-7)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1987 (Box-folder 41-8)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1988 (Box-folder 41-9)
  - Photographic negatives – Baseball, 1988 (Box-folder 41-10)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 41-11)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 41-12)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 41-13)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 41-14)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 41-15)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 41-16)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 41-17)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 41-18)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41-19)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 41-20)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 42-1)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Men, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 42-2)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 42-3)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 42-4)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 42-5)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 42-6)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 42-7)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 42-8)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 42-9)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 42-10)
  - Photographic negatives – Basketball, Women, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 42-11)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1979 (Box-folder 42-12)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1980 (Box-folder 42-13)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1981 (Box-folder 42-14)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1985 (Box-folder 42-15)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1986 (Box-folder 42-16)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1987 (Box-folder 42-17)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1988 (Box-folder 43-1)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1989 (Box-folder 43-2)
  - Photographic negatives – Football, 1990 (Box-folder 43-3)
  - Photographic negatives – Swimming, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 43-4)
  - Photographic negatives – Swimming, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 43-5)
  - Photographic negatives – Swimming, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 43-6)
  - Photographic negatives – Swimming, 1985 (Box-folder 43-7)
  - Photographic negatives – Swimming, 1986 (Box-folder 43-8)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1980 (Box-folder 43-9)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1981 (Box-folder 43-10)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1982 (Box-folder 43-11)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1983 (Box-folder 43-12)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1984 (Box-folder 43-13)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1985 (Box-folder 43-14)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1986 (Box-folder 43-15)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1987 (Box-folder 43-16)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1988 (Box-folder 43-17)
  - Photographic negatives – Track and Field, 1989 (Box-folder 43-18)
  - Photographs – Baseball, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 44-1)
  - Photographs – Basketball, Men, 1990s-2001 (Box-folder 44-2)
  - Photographs – Basketball, Women, 2000 (Box-folder 44-3)
  - Photographs – Football (unidentified), 1980-1990 (Box-folder 44-4)
  - Photographs – Football (unidentified), 1980-1990 (Box-folder 44-5)
  - Photographs – Football (unidentified), 1980-1990 (Box-folder 44-6)
  - Photographs – Football, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 44-7)
  - Photographs – Football, 2000 (Box-folder 44-8)
  - Photographs – Football (individuals), 2000 (Box-folder 44-9)
  - Photographs – Football (individuals), 2001 (Box-folder 44-10)
  - Photographs – Football (individuals), 2001 (Box-folder 44-11)
  - Photographs – Soccer, Women, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 44-12)
  - Photographs – Softball, 2001 (Box-folder 44-13)
  - Photographs – Softball, 2002 (Box-folder 44-14)
  - Photographs – Track and Field, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 45-1)
  - Photographs – Volleyball, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 45-2)
  - Photographs – Women’s Soccer, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 45-3)
  - Photographs – Wrestling, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 45-4)
  - Miscellaneous negatives (Box-folder 45-5)
  - Miscellaneous slides (Box-folder 45-6)
- Video Cassettes of Sporting Events, IX
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), 1988 (Box-item 46-1)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Simon Fraser University (Football), October 21, 1989 (Box-item 46-2)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Whitworth College (Football), November 4, 1989 (Box-item 46-3)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon State College (Football), November 11, 1989 (Box-item 46-4)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Dickinson College (N.D.) (Football), December 2, 1989 (Box-item 46-5)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Westminster College (Pa.) (Football), December 9, 1989 (Box-item 46-6)
  - Videos – Recruiting Highlight Tape (Football), 1990 (Box-item 46-7)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon State College (Football), September 15, 1990 (Box-item 46-8)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Linfield College (Football), September 22, 1990 (Box-item 46-9)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Linfield College (Football), September 22, 1990 (Box-item 46-10)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Football), September 29, 1990 (Box-item 46-11)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 6, 1990 (Box-item 46-12)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University(Football), October 6, 1990 (Box-item 46-13)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon University (Football), October 13, 1990 (Box-item 46-14)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon University (Football), October 13, 1990 (Box-item 46-15)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Simon Fraser University (Football), October 20, 1990 (Box-item 46-16)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 27, 1990 (Box-item 46-17)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Whitworth College (Football), November 3, 1990 (Box-item 46-18)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Oregon Institute of Technology (Football), September 21, 1991 (Box-item 46-19)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Oregon Institute of Technology (Football), September 21, 1991 (Box-item 46-20)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 12, 1991 (Box-item 46-21)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 26, 1991 (Box-item 46-22)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 26, 1991 (Box-item 46-23)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Football), November 16, 1991 (Box-item 46-24)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), November 23, 1991 (Box-item 46-25)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University(Football), November 23, 1991 (Box-item 46-26)
  - Videos – Football Highlight Tape (Football), 1991 (Box-item 46-27)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Oregon Institute of Technology (Football), September 19, 1992 (Box-item 46-28)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon State College (Football), September 26, 1992 (Box-item 46-29)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon State College (Football), September 26, 1992 (Box-item 46-30)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 10, 1992 (Box-item 46-31)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 10, 1992 (Box-item 46-32)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), October 17, 1992 (Box-item 46-33)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), October 17, 1992 (Box-item 46-34)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University(Football), October 24, 1992 (Box-item 46-35)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 24, 1992 (Box-item 46-36)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Simon Fraser University (Football), November 7, 1992 (Box-item 46-37)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Football), November 14, 1992 (Box-item 46-38)
  - Videos – Banquet Highlights Tape (Football), 1992 (Box-item 46-39)
  - Videos – Weekly Highlights Tape (Football), 1992 (Box-item 46-40)
  - Videos – Defensive Highlights Tape (Football), 1990-1992 (Box-item 46-41)
  - Videos – Recruiting Tape, Highlights (Football), 1990-1992 (Box-item 46-42)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), September 18, 1993 (Box-item 46-43)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), September 18, 1993 (Box-item 46-44)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon State College (Football), September 25, 1993 (Box-item 47-1)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Lewis and Clark College (Football), October 2, 1993 (Box-item 47-2)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Lewis and Clark College (Football), October 2, 1993 (Box-item 47-3)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Linfield College (Football), October 9, 1993 (Box-item 47-4)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Linfield College (Football), October 9, 1993 (Box-item 47-5)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 16, 1993 (Box-item 47-6)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Whitworth College (Football), October 23, 1993 (Box-item 47-7)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Whitworth College (Football), October 23, 1993 (Box-item 47-8)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Simon Fraser University (Football), November 6, 1993 (Box-item 47-9)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 30, 1993 (Box-item 47-10)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), December 4, 1993 (Box-item 47-11)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), December 4, 1993 (Box-item 47-12)
  - Videos – Highlight Tape (Football), 1993 (Box-item 47-13)
  - Videos – Highlight Tape (Football), 1993 (Box-item 47-14)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon University (Football), September 17, 1994 (Box-item 47-15)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon State College (Football), September 24, 1994 (Box-item 47-16)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon State College (Football), September 24, 1994 (Box-item 47-17)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Lewis and Clark College (Football), October 1, 1994 (Box-item 47-18)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Lewis and Clark College (Football), October 1, 1994 (Box-item 47-19)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Linfield College (Football), October 8, 1994 (Box-item 47-20)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Linfield College (Football), October 8, 1994 (Box-item 47-21)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 15, 1994 (Box-item 47-22)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 15, 1994 (Box-item 47-23)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 29, 1994 (Box-item 47-24)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Simon Fraser University (Football), November 5, 1994 (Box-item 47-25)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Football), November 12, 1994 (Box-item 47-26)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Football), November 12, 1994 (Box-item 47-27)
  - Videos – Highlight Tape (Football), 1994 (Box-item 47-28)
  - Videos – Scrimmage game no.1 (Football), 1995 (Box-item 47-29)
  - Videos – Scrimmage game no.2 (Football), 1995 (Box-item 47-30)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Montana State University (Football), September 9, 1995 (Box-item 47-31)